<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pascals Blog</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/</link><description>Recent content on Pascals Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 01:14:24 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ppeinecke.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-CTF - Web - Favourite Website</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-web-favourite-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 01:14:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-web-favourite-website/</guid><description>Web - Favourite Website - writeup Description After a long time, Alex tries to visit his favorite website. But nobody thought he would become very unlucky. Visit the website and help him get the flag.
Link: https://wec-ctf-2022-web.herokuapp.com/q2
Writeup If we refresh the webpage we see there is a cookie that changes everytime i refresh the page.
That cookie is called _gatj
Currently its value is c3RpbGwgY2Fubm90IHNvbHZlIHRoaXMgdGFzaz90aW1lcz0wMDAwMDAwOCZpZD03Yzg3ZjBlOC1hODNiLTQyZDQtYmU1MS1hYWI5MjY5MzRjYzI3
That is base64 and decodes to still cannot solve this task?</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Osint - Vacation</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-osint-vacation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 01:07:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-osint-vacation/</guid><description>Osint - Vacation - Writeup Description People even try to turn their pets into celebrities, it gets annoying quite fast. That reminds me, have you come across @tig3r_and_b3ar ? Apparently their owner is a photographer, I haven’t contacted her though.
Writeup Since the owner is a photographer we should look at instagram.
By using an instagram viewer we can look at her profile without actually logging in.
The one thing that sticks out here is that this account is following exactly one other account.</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Misc - What Is This</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-misc-what-is-this/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:58:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-misc-what-is-this/</guid><description>Misc - whatisthis - writeup Description Intelligence has found same weird material from Mr. Codeshankar (yes,him again). So it is your task now to find out whats contained in it. The link is here !(https://drive.google.com/file/d/1fFAexozA987VAgDI2AnOcr4ei2TLUO6Q/view?usp=sharing)[]
Writeup after unpacking the zip file whatisthis.zip I get an image file whatisthis.png
The file itself is broken and cannot be opened.
After checking with the file command what that file actually is I am presented with the following: whatisthis.</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Forensics - THE CAT KNOWS THE CULPRIT</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-the-cat-knows-the-culprit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:36:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-the-cat-knows-the-culprit/</guid><description>Forensics - THE CAT KNOWS THE CULPRIT writeup Description Detective Jake Peralta and his partner Charles Boyle are assigned a Grand Larceny case, by their captain Raymond Holt. Upon their arrival to crime scene they find that there are no clues for them to catch the victim, so they leave the crime scene and at the exif exit door they find an image along with a note saying &amp;ldquo;THE CAT KNOWS THE CULPRIT.</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Forensics - I Can Do This All Day</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-can-do-this-all-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:16:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-can-do-this-all-day/</guid><description>Forensics - I can do this all day - writeup Description Tony Stark: a hacker who&amp;rsquo;s faster than ultron? he could be anywhere GLOBAL. And as this is the center of everything, I&amp;rsquo;m just a REGULAR guy looking for a needle in the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest haystack.
World Hub Tech: How do you find it? Tony Stark: pretty simple. you bring a magnet.
Flag format: CTF{&amp;hellip;}
Writeup cat *.txt | grep CTF</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Forensics - I Am Groot</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-am-groot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 20:39:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-am-groot/</guid><description>Forensics - I am Groot - writeup Description Send the right message to get your flag from Groot.
Check the discord server, !groot will call the bot.
Hint: We are friends
Writeup Once I tried to dm the bot directly with: !groot rocket
I get
01001001 00100000 01100001 01101101 00100000 01000111 01110010 01101111 01101111 01110100 00100001
Lets convert that binary to ascii
that is binary and coverts to
I am Groot!</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/about/</guid><description>Hello!
I am Pascal Peinecke, Student of Applied Computer Sciences at Hochschule Niederrhein and information security enthusiast based in Ratingen, Germany.
On this blog I will publish all of my security related writeups from CTFs, crackmes, HTB machines, etc</description></item><item><title>Contact Me</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/contact/</guid><description>The Force is strong with this one. I have you now. I find your lack of faith disturbing. Hey, Luke! May the Force be with you. She must have hidden the plans in the escape pod. Send a detachment down to retrieve them, and see to it personally, Commander. There’ll be no one to stop us this time!</description></item><item><title>Style Guide</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/styleguide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/styleguide/</guid><description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.
Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description></item></channel></rss>