<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pascals Blog</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/</link><description>Recent content on Pascals Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:16:36 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ppeinecke.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-CTF - Forensics - I Can Do This All Day</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-can-do-this-all-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:16:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-can-do-this-all-day/</guid><description>Forensics - I can do this all day - writeup cat *.txt | grep CTF
CTF{d3cry471ng_nu3l34r_c0d35}
So by simply just simply cat&amp;rsquo;ing all of the files in the different directories we got the flag. Easy.</description></item><item><title>E-CTF - Forensics - I Am Groot</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-am-groot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 20:39:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/posts/ectf-forensics-i-am-groot/</guid><description>Forensics - I am Groot - writeup Once I tried to dm the bot directly with: !groot rocket
I get
01001001 00100000 01100001 01101101 00100000 01000111 01110010 01101111 01101111 01110100 00100001
Lets convert that binary to ascii
that is binary and coverts to
I am Groot!
Once i try to dm the bot with: !groot pascal
I get :
SSBhbSBHcm9vdCE=
That is base64 and translates to: I am Groot!
Lol</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/about/</guid><description>Hello!
I am Pascal Peinecke, Student of Applied Computer Sciences at Hochschule Niederrhein and information security enthusiast based in Ratingen, Germany.
On this blog I will publish all of my security related writeups from CTFs, crackmes, HTB machines, etc</description></item><item><title>Contact Me</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/contact/</guid><description>The Force is strong with this one. I have you now. I find your lack of faith disturbing. Hey, Luke! May the Force be with you. She must have hidden the plans in the escape pod. Send a detachment down to retrieve them, and see to it personally, Commander. There’ll be no one to stop us this time!</description></item><item><title>Style Guide</title><link>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/styleguide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.ppeinecke.de/styleguide/</guid><description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.
Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description></item></channel></rss>